Hello
Hello friends Welcome to Taste Rice Friends,
the news we waited for has finally arrived The quarter final result of IT
sector giant TCS has
come and along with it the
company has declared a difference for its shareholders
So
let's quickly see
how its result has been this time for our readers and
how much difference the company is giving to its country
So friends we have come to the
quarter final result of TCS here
First of all you will get a difference in rupees per share
but this difference
is the final decision so first the
approval of the share holder is very important in this, the
approval of the share holder will be received then only their
shareholders will get the difference But let me tell you that if
99.99 percent approval is received then this
boiled Surya Dev will get them So there is
no need to take tension Here we have
kept the PC quarter for Kerala
Here you first see whatever
number I have written in crores, it is
written here you can see by the way these letters are
very small to look at  You might be having trouble,
but let me adjust it a little. Yes, it might have become a
little clear now. This is the
company's performance this time, meaning the quarter for the company.
This is the performance of Q3 of last year.
And this is the quarter for last year. But
we have given it here.
You can see that we will first
start with the review from operations, which
was 42,705 crores last year, which has
increased to
50,500.91 crores in this quarter and in the previous quarter it was
48,885 crores. So you can say that the
revenue from operations is
showing very good growth
year after year and quarter after quarter. Now if other
income is added to it, then the total income of TCS this time will be
51,572 crores,
which was
44,600.36 crores last year and it was
1,090 crores in the previous quarter. So you can say that
TCS is seeing growth in its performance both year after year and quarter after quarter,
which is a very good
thing. But friends, just by looking at the income,  It's
also very important for us to look at the company's expenses. So, the
full total
is written here. You can see that
expenses are increasing slightly this year compared to last year,
and they've
also increased slightly from the previous quarter.
But that's okay. If income is being generated,
expenses will also increase slightly. This is normal.
Now, look here, profit
protection means the profit that remains in the company's hands after the remaining expenses
and before paying taxes. This is
written here. TCS's profit before taxes is Rs.
3364 crore, which was Rs. 12500 crore last year
and Rs. 13191 crore in the previous quarter.
So, you can say that we are seeing a
good growth,
we are seeing another quarter of underwater growth as well. Now, the
company's main profit is written here.
Look at this, I'll estimate it so that
you can understand the numbers better. So, this is TCS
's main profit this year,
after expenses etc.  After giving all the details,
whatever is left in the hands of the company
is Rs
9959 crore, which was Rs 99,282 crore last year
and Rs
9806 crore in the previous quarter. We are seeing
TCS's profit increasing here, both from last year and from the previous quarter. So, we are
seeing more growth in its performance. Whatever may be the estimate of this company, whatever may be the
estimate, whether it has
come down from Hanuman
or increased from Hanuman, it does
not matter because TCS is a very
good company. Even if one or two of its regions go bad, it does not
matter.
Now let me take a look at the company's app here. Let
me adjust it a little.
Look, it is written here that last
year it was 24.97 and in the previous quarter it was
426.41, which has become
26.85 in this quarter. So you
can say that friend, and in Air and Water and Quarter
Peace, a good growth is also being seen. According to
me, in the third quarter for  My career has been
good, I would not like to display it.
This share is also in my portfolio. I am going to
fold it. If you also have a
problem, then you can also fold it. So
friends, if you liked the information, then do
like this video
and if you are new to the channel, then do
subscribe to this channel so that the
quarterly update of your favorite company can
reach you quickly. So that is all for now.
We will meet in the next video. Till then,
goodbye.